真不知道我这些年来
I don't know why I avoided
为什么不看哈利波特系列小说
the Harry Potter books for so long.
写得很不错啊
These are great.
我刚开始看第六册
I just started number six.
那本挺好看的
That's a good one.
邓布利多在这一本里死了
Dumbledore dies in that one.
我懂你的感觉  我当初也没料到
Yeah, I know, I didn't see it coming, either.
你干嘛说出来啊
Why would you say that?
你开始了一个话题
You brought up the subject.
然后我回以与话题有关的有趣讯息
I contributed an interesting fact on that subject.
这就叫聊天的艺术啊
It's called the art of conversation.
换你说了
Okay, your turn.
你这是超级大剧透啊
That was a huge spoiler.
灰常好
Good.
你这人有病啊
What is wrong with you?
换做是我剧透  你肯定会叽歪一整周
If I did that, you'd bitch about it for weeks.
不是吧  莱纳德
Oh, really, Leonard?
你的小暴脾气又要发作了吗
Are you going to have another one of your hissy fits?
小暴脾气  我有小暴脾气吗
Hissy fits? I have hissy fits?
没错  而且我还得出个推论
Yes, and I have a theory why.
因为你的乳糖不耐症
Because of your lactose intolerance,
所以你用豆奶替代牛奶
you switched over to soy milk.
而大豆含有类雌激素的化合物
Soy contains estrogen-mimicking compounds.
你的可可球加豆奶早餐
I think your morning Cocoa Puffs
把你变成了一个歇斯底里的八婆
are turning you into a hysterical woman.
你还真够极品啊
You are unbelievable.
我干嘛要这么忍你
I don't know why I put up with you.
又是控制狂  又超级欠扁
You're controlling, you're irritating...
又开始叽叽歪歪了  叽叽  歪歪  叽歪
There you go again-- nag, nag, nag.
越叽歪越显得我说得对哦  小三八
You're only proving my point, little lady.
谢尔顿  滚你丫的
You know what? Screw you, Sheldon.
你是我这辈子见过最烦人的人了
You are the most annoying person I have ever met.
什么  我哪里烦人了
What? I'm annoying?
明明是你整天对我的言行意见超多
You criticize my behavior all the time.
"谢尔顿  吃早饭时别提你排便的事"
"Sheldon, don't talk about your bowel movements over breakfast."
"谢尔顿  我们大学校长
"Sheldon, when the president of the university
在丧礼上念悼词时
is giving a eulogy at a funeral,
别打哈欠外加指手表催他"
don't yawn and point at your watch."
"谢尔顿  不要觉得我衣服难看
"Sheldon, don't throw away my shirts
就把它们拿去丢了"
'cause you think they're ugly."
你才难搞好吗
You're impossible.
够了  我没必要...
That's it. I don't...
我没必要忍这些极品事
I don't have to put up with this.
事实上  从你在室友协议上签名的那天起
Actually, I have your signature on a roommate agreement
你就注定得忍受
that says you do.
这就是我对室友协议的意见
Here's what I think of your roommate agreement.
-你马上给我捡起来  -不要
- You pick that up right now. - No.
室友协议第27章  第五段写明
Roommate agreement, section 27, paragraph 5:
室友协议书  与美国国旗一样
The roommate agreement, like the American flag,
都不许落地
cannot touch the ground.
懒得鸟你
I don't care.
我才懒得管你说了哪些屁话呢
I don't have to do anything you say because...
我以后不想住这里了
I don't think I want to live here anymore.
-你要上哪去  -去跟佩妮住
- Where are you going? - To live with Penny
不跟你这傻逼混球住了
and not you, you crazy bastard.
-你骂我傻逼混球  -没错
- Crazy bastard? - Yes.
-莱纳德  等等  -干嘛
- Leonard, wait. - What?
小精灵多比在第七册也死了
Dobby the elf dies in book seven.
生活大爆炸
第六季  第十四集
还你
Here you go.
太好啦  进来吧
Great. Come on in.
连句谢谢都不说吗
What, you don't say thank you?
这本来就是我的
It's my suitcase.
我两年前借给你的
I lent it to you two years ago.
行  那我告诉你吧
Well, then, I should tell you
我把轮子跟手把都弄坏了
I broke the wheel and the handle.
伯纳黛特全公司的人
So, is everyone from Bernadette's company
都要去赌城玩吗
going to Vegas?
没  就我跟她  以及一些高层
No, just me, her and a couple of the big wigs.
-这是她公司的额外奖励啦  -不错
- It's part of a bonus she got. - Cool.
她是研发出某种疾病的解药之类的吗
Did she discover a cure for something?
不算是啦
Not exactly.
他们公司砸大钱研发出一种治疗头皮屑的药
They spent a ton of money developing this dandruff medication
而那个药的副作用是导致严重拉稀
that had the side effect of horrible anal leakage.
难道拉稀还能是好事吗
Is there a good anal leakage?
反正是妮妮的主意
Anyway, it was Bernie's idea
让公司把这药物当成治便秘的药物销售
to rebrand the stuff as a cure for constipation.
好一条赚钱路子[做柠檬水]啊
Way to make lemonade.
靠人家做巧克力软糕[拉屎]赚钱
You know, from around the corner where fudge is made.
-我有件事想请你帮忙  -说吧
- Hey, I got a favor to ask. - Sure.
我妈被之前好上的那牙医抛弃之后
My mom's been kind of an emotional wreck
心情就落到了谷底  郁郁寡欢
since that dentist she was dating dumped her.
抛弃她  得用叉车才能吧
Dumped her? What, did he use a forklift?
对不起
Sorry.
不应该取笑病态肥胖的人
There's nothing funny about morbid obesity.
她肥爆了  是很好笑啦
She's huge. It was funny.
我是希望呢
Anyway, I was just hoping
你明晚能去她那里  看看她
that maybe you could check in on her tomorrow night
确保以下她没事
and make sure she's doing okay.
兄弟  我可是黄金单身汉
Dude, I'm a single man.
周六夜是我的狂欢夜呢
Saturday night is my party night.
是吗  你有什么安排
Really? What do you got going on?
不知道  可能开车去好莱坞那里
I don't know, maybe drive down to Hollywood,
去几个泡妞圣地转转  看有无妹子上钩
hit a few hot spots, see if I can get lucky.
告诉我这个场景你是否似曾相识
Okay, tell me if this sounds familiar.
你花了15块停车费
You pay $15 to park,
然后站在人行道一个小时犹豫
you stand on the sidewalk for an hour
直到你忍不住  然后给了门卫
until you break down and give the bouncer
20块门票费  让你进去
20 bucks to let you in.
你努力挤到吧台
You push your way to the bar,
喝杯18块的大都会鸡尾酒
where you drink an $18 cosmopolitan,
然后盯着一个美女
then you stare at a pretty girl
在脑海中幻想你们一起的美好人生
and imagine your perfect life together.
幻想你们的孩子  孙子
Your children, grandchildren.
然后看着她被自称是电影
Meanwhile, she leaves with a guy who claims
《比佛利拜金狗》编剧的男人给泡走
he wrote Beverly Hills Chihuahua.
然后你就自暴自弃
Then you give up on anyone ever loving you,
跑去连锁派店买了个派
go to Marie Callender's, buy a pie
然后回到停车场  在车上默默吃掉它
and eat it in your car in the parking lot.
我明天该几点到你妈家来着
What time should I be at your mother's?
我跟她说你晚上7点到
I told her around 7:00.
我发誓  那家伙是我这辈子见过
I swear, that man is the most egotistical,
最傲慢自大  最难以忍受的人类
insufferable human being I have ever met.
话是没错  但你们这对很有爱呢
Yeah, but you two make such a cute couple.
《芝麻街》的两个木偶角色
同住在一起  虽然经常吵架但又很快和好
就像伯特和厄尼
Like Burt and Ernie.
你们俩甚至还教我词语和数字
You guys even teach me stuff about words and numbers.
《芝麻街》是美国家喻户晓的儿童教育节目
教授基础阅读算术 颜色的名称 字母和数字等基本知识
我受够了  真的够了
Well, I've had it. I am done.
我连跟他同住多一分钟都忍不了
I can't... I can't live with him for one more minute.
那你打算去哪里住
Where are you going to go?
来这里跟你住啊
I was thinking here with you.
有问题吗
That a problem?
没有  完全没有
No, not at all.
真没  这样很好啊
No, it's-it's great.
简直太棒了
It's terrific. I...
我只是忍不住替谢尔顿难过而已
You know, I just can't help feel bad about Sheldon.
我是觉得...
I mean...
他没有你怎么活啊
how's he going to get by without you?
厄尼
Ernie.
他现在有艾米了
He's got Amy now.
的确  但不一样的啦
Yeah, he does, but it's not the same.
为什么
Why?
好吧  这么说吧
Well, um, all right.
在《哈利·波特与混血王子》[第六册]中
You-you know how in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince,
罗恩没有因为哈利  跟自己妹妹恋爱
Ron didn't abandon Harry just because Harry started
而抛弃哈利啊
dating Ron's sister?
哈利和金妮在一起了啊
Harry and Ginny get together?
抱歉  剧透警告
Sorry. Spoiler alert.
我的重点是  尽管我很想跟你住在一起
My point is, as much as I want to live with you,
但谢尔顿需要你  我不能这么自私
I can't do it knowing how much Sheldon needs you.
拜托  他唯一需要我的地方是
Please, the only thing he needs me for
当他的替罪羔羊
is to be his whipping boy,
他的傀儡和出气筒
his-his stooge, his doormat.
人家不是都说 "不要没事找事嘛"
Well, you know what they say: if it ain't broke...
源自谚语"If it ain't broke, don't fix it"
意思是不要随便改变现状  小心弄巧成拙
听起来似乎你不想咱俩住在一起
It sounds to me like you don't want us to live together.
不  不是  我想
No. No, no, I do.
我当然想  只是...
I do. It's just...
这可是很重要的一步
I mean, it's a really big step.
是吗
Is it?
我们总是在一起
We're together all the time.
钱方面来看  同住好处多多啊
Financially, it makes great sense.
你能想出一个我们不该住在一起的理由吗
Can you think of one reason why we shouldn't do this?
这个嘛...
Well... um...
-我突然有点口渴  -喝吧
- I'm just a little thirsty. - Yeah.
想不到
I got nothing.
很好  我去收拾东西
Great. I'll go get my stuff.
好
Good.
好吧  别慌别慌
Okay, all right, don't freak out.
你能搞定这件事的
You can make this work.
你能帮我在浴室整理出一个架子放东西吗
Oh, could you clear off a shelf for me in the bathroom?
我每天要吃超多药
I take a lot of medicine.
拜托一定要有抗焦虑的药
Oh, please let some of it be Xanax.
准备好要吃甜点了吗
Are you ready for dessert?
不了  谢谢  沃罗威茨太太
No, thank you, Mrs. Wolowitz.
老实说  我撑得都要抱着肚子走出去了
As it is, I'm going to have to carry my stomach out of here
就像消防员小心翼翼地救出婴儿那样
like I'm a fireman rescuing an infant.
拜托
Oh, please.
你是个又高又瘦的帅阿三
You're a tall glass of brown water.
吃了甜点再走吧
Have dessert.
我真的吃不下了
Well, I-I really couldn't.
但我今晚过得很开心  边吃你炖的牛胸肉
But, uh, I've had a lovely time eating your brisket
边听你说你这些年从自己身上
and hearing about the things you've had removed
切除下来的各种东西
from your body over the years.
真不知道原来肿瘤里能长出瘤中瘤
Didn't know you could have a cyst inside another cyst.
医生说它们就像俄罗斯的套娃一样
The doctor said they were like Russian nesting dolls.
如果你坚持要走
Well, if you have to go,
那我把东西打包到一起让你带走吧
how about I put a little doggie bag together for you?
那真是太好了  谢谢你
That would be lovely. Thank you.
沃罗威茨太太
Mrs. Wolowitz, uh...
你没事吧
are you okay?
别理我
Don't mind me.
我一觉得孤单
I just cry when I'm lonely
没什么活头  就会想哭
and have nothing to live for.
要不...
I, uh...
-要不我吃完甜点再走吧  -太好了
- I suppose I could stay for some dessert. - Great.
-你喜欢吃巧克力碎乳酪蛋糕吗  -喜欢
- You like chocolate chip cheesecake? - Sure.
那我做一个
I'll make one.
一个捣蛋先生古董模型玩偶
One vintage Mr. Mxyzptlk action figure.
《超人漫画》里面的角色
来自其他宇宙  以戏弄超人为乐
莱纳德的
That's Leonard's.
儿童玩具
Children's toy.
一把《星际迷航:下一代》里的相位枪
One Star Trek: The Next Genxtion phaser.
莱纳德的
That's Leonard's.
儿童玩具
Children's toy.
一把《权力的游戏》收藏版长爪剑
One Game of Thrones collector's edition Longclaw sword.
莱纳德和我一起买的
Oh... Leonard and I bought that together.
这是个伦理难题
That's a bit of an ethical conundrum.
算了  我留着吧
Eh, I'll keep it.
你接下来有什么计划
So, uh, what's your plan moving forward?
估计我得找一个新室友  然后教化他
Uh, suppose I'll have to find and cultivate a new roommate.
这是一项多么艰巨的任务啊
What a task that will be.
你知道莱纳德一开始进来住的时候多没教养吗
Do you know how uncivilized Leonard was when I took him in?
不知道
No.
废了好大功夫  才让他有固定的如厕时间
Oh, it took me forever to get him on a bathroom schedule.
他以前只要感觉一来  想去就去
He would just go whenever the mood struck him.
-就像小狗整天拉撒  -完全正确
- Like a dog-boy. - Exactly.
假设你能找到一个室友
What if you could find a roommate
既是科学家
who was a scientist
同时熟悉并喜欢你的生活方式
and already familiar and comfortable with your ways?
那当然最理想啦
That would be ideal.
如果真有那么一个人存在
If a person like that existed,
我会什么都不问  立马签协议
I would sign on, no further questions asked.
太好了  那个人近在眼前
Great. Here I am!
等等
Wait.
那个人是谁  眼前是哪里
Here who is where?
我啊
Me.
我难道不是最佳室友人选吗
Aren't I your perfect roommate?
好好想想  谢尔顿
Think about it, Sheldon.
我既不是陌生人
I'm not a stranger,
我们的智商又是同一等级
we're intellectually compatible,
我愿意开车载你满城转
I'm willing to chauffeur you around town,
还有你个性怪癖
and your personality quirks,
别人会觉得厌恶或烦人
which others find abhorrent or rage-inducing,
而我却觉得超级可爱
I find cute as a button.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
告诉我一个你觉得这主意不棒的理由
Tell me one reason why this isn't a fantastic idea.
看  你想不到吧
See? You can't.
我去看看莱纳德的房间
I'm gonna go see if Leonard's room
够不够放我的水床
is big enough for my water bed.
好兄弟莱纳德  好兄弟莱纳德
Good buddy Leonard. Good buddy Leonard.
好兄弟莱纳德
Good buddy Leonard.
干嘛
What do you want?
好兄弟  你好啊
Hey, good buddy.
我刚和艾米聊了聊
So, uh, I was just talking to Amy,
她让我意识到
and she made me realize
我和你这次的小纠纷
that this little dust-up between you and me
根本就不足挂齿
is much ado about nothing.
-是吗  -是的
- Is that so? - Yes.
我原谅你了  回家来吧
All is forgiven, so come back home.
我给你做一杯热巧克力豆奶
I'll make you some soy hot chocolate,
然后再给你说说我们激动人心的
and then I'll you tell you about our exciting new
想拉就拉的如厕新政策
devil-may-care bathroom policy.
-别拐弯抹角了  谢尔顿  -好吧
- Cut to the chase, Sheldon. - Okay.
艾米说要搬进来住
Amy's decided she wants to move in with me,
所以我需要你回家  你个可爱的小调皮
so I need you to come back home, you lovable scamp.
头上抹好多东西啊
That's a lot of product.
-怎么了  -是这样的
- What's going on? - Oh, get this:
谢尔顿突然又想让我回去了
suddenly, Sheldon wants me back
因为艾米想搬进去和他一起住
because Amy wants to move in with him.
是吗  真有意思
Really? Interesting.
太晚了  伙计  我哪也不去
Well, too late, pal. I'm not going anywhere.
佩妮和我在一起非常幸福快乐
Penny and I are very happy living together.
对吗
Isn't that right?
就像是幸福要赖在这公寓里不走了呢
It's like the happiness won't ever leave the apartment.
莱纳德  拜托了
Leonard, please.
你知道艾米搬进来就意味着我们要面对
You know Amy moving in marks a level of intimacy
我们压根没准备好的亲密关系
our relationship isn't ready for.
没错  这事真有其事
Yes! That is a real thing.
这不代表你们不在乎彼此
And it doesn't mean you don't care about each other;
只是这种节奏
it just means things are moving at a pace
让你感到不安  这很正常
you're not comfortable with, and that's fine.
如果他不想和她一起住
Well, if he doesn't want to live with her,
那他就应该当面讲清楚
then he should tell her how he feels.
也许他是不知道要怎样说
Well, maybe he doesn't know how to say it
才能不伤害她的感情
without hurting her feelings.
感情
Feelings?
你以为我是嬉皮士在谈情说爱啊  不是的
What am I, a hippie at a love-in? No.
问题是
The problem is,
她说出了一系列我根本无法反驳的
she laid out a series of logical arguments
逻辑论证
that I couldn't refute.
-这样最糟糕了  对吗  -没错
- That is the worst, isn't it? - Yes.
抱歉  谢尔顿  我无能为力
I'm sorry, Sheldon. I can't help you.
剧透警告
Oh, spoiler alert:
这门要摔你脸上了
this door's about to slam in your face.
你在这啊
Oh, there you are.
我什么时候能拿到"我们家"的钥匙呀
When do I get a key to our apartment?
你好
Hello?
是我  昨晚和我妈处得怎么样
Hey. How'd it go last night with my mom?
挺好的
Okay, I guess.
你什么时候走的
What time did you leave?
事实上我还在这
Actually, I'm still here.
什么  你在我家过夜了啊
What? You spent the night?
是啊
Yeah.
晚饭后  我们看了《罗克福德档案》的重播
After dinner, we watched a rerun of Rockford Files,
然后她开了一瓶
and then she opened a bottle
奶油雪利酒  然后不知不觉
of, uh, cream sherry, and the next thing I know,
她就把我哄上你的床睡觉了
she was tucking me into your bed.
你穿的是我的睡衣吗
You wore my pajamas?
你平时到底怎么睡的啊
How do you sleep in these things?
真丝睡衣配绸缎床单
Silk pajamas on satin sheets?
我滑下床三次了都
I slid out of the bed, like, three times.
拉杰什
Rajesh!
你起来了吗
You up?
准备好吃早饭了吗
You ready for breakfast?
这么好  有早饭
Oh, boy. Breakfast.
拉杰  听我说
Okay, Raj, listen to me.
你得马上走
You need to get out of there.
但我的奶油酒宿醉还没退
But I have a cream sherry hangover
而且我还闻到薄饼卷的味道了
and I smell blintzes.
如果你现在不走
If you don't leave now,
她就会利用食物和你的愧疚感
she'll use food and guilt
让你后半辈子一直困在那
to keep you there for the rest of your life.
霍华德  别说了
Oh, Howard, stop.
相信我  你不是犹太人
Trust me, you're not Jewish.
犹太人就是这么收服人的
That's how they get you.
你别说傻话了
You're being silly.
我想什么时候走就能什么时候走
I can leave whenever I want.
是吗  那你的衣服和鞋在哪呢
Oh, really? Where are your clothes and your shoes?
在椅子上呢  就在...
They're on the chair, right over...
糟糕[犹太人用语]
Oy vey.
你好  家庭破坏者
Hello, home wrecker.
我怎么了
What did I do?
你给了莱纳德退路
You gave Leonard somewhere to go.
就因为你
Thanks to you,
艾米现在去买情侣浴巾了
Amy's out buying his and hers bath towels.
就好像我真会用上面写有
Like I'd ever dry myself with something
所有格代名词的东西擦身子似的
that has a possessive pronoun on it.
听我说
Okay, listen.
其实我根本不想跟他住
The truth is I don't want him living with me.
太好了  那把他赶出来
Great. Kick him out.
伤他的心  皆大欢喜
Break his heart. Everybody wins.
不  我不想伤他的心
No, I don't want to break his heart.
我爱他
I love him.
但他搬过来让我很措手不及
This is just happening too fast.
这就叫措手不及啊
You think this is fast?
要不了多久我的洗澡间
It's just a matter of time
就能看见艾米掉的腿毛了
before I see Amy's leg stubble in my shower.
我可见过她的腿
Yeah, and I've seen those legs.
你最好准备点管道疏通剂
You might want to get some Drano.
等一下
Hold on.
如果你不想和莱纳德一起住
If you don't want to live with Leonard,
那你为什么不跟他直说
why don't you just tell him?
你知道他这个人
Well, you know how he is.
又敏感  又感性
He's sensitive and emotional.
那是因为他喝太多豆奶了
That's because he drinks too much soy milk.
不过除了告诉他们事实
Well, I don't know what else we can do
我也想不出其他办法了
but tell them the truth.
看来我们必须得
I suppose there's no choice
面对他们泪如雨下  怒发苛责
but to face the crying, angry accusations
以及尖声绝望的哀嚎
and the high-pitched wails of despair.
对啊
Yeah.
而艾米的反应就不知道了
And who knows how Amy will react.
冰来了
Here's some more ice.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
我们脑子进水了吗
What were we thinking?
按正常方式来做不就行了嘛
We should have just done it the regular way.
太阳马戏团里的中国杂技演员
Those Chinese acrobats in Cirque du Soleil
做起来感觉超轻松啊
made it look so easy.
不过说实话  如果我的腰能弯成那样
Honestly, if I could bend that far,
我还用得着你吗
what would I need with you?
如果你的腰能弯成那样  那咱俩省事多了
If you could bend that far, you'd be doing us both a favor.
拉杰  还好吗
Hey, Raj. What's up?
你太对了
You were right!
我逃不掉了
I can't get out of here!
你还在我妈家吗
You're still at my mother's?
我被困在这里了
I'm trapped.
我的衣服已经洗了一整天了
My clothes have been in the laundry all day,
而且钥匙也被她藏起来了
and she hid my keys.
我觉得有可能在她的文胸里
I think they might be in her bra,
因为她走起路来叮当响
because she jingles when she walks.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
你不是希望生命中有个女人吗
Hey, you wanted a woman in your life.
现在如愿啦
Now you got one.
拜托  霍华德  救命啊
Come on, Howard, help me.
拉杰什  宝贝  洗澡水放好了
Rajesh, tatellah, I ran you a bath.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
她不会想帮我洗澡吧
She's not gonna bathe me, is she?
老天  我真希望能告诉你她不会
Gee, I wish I could tell you no.
好吧  再次多谢你帮忙
All right, well, thanks again for helping me out.
但是  霍华德
But, Howard...
我们应该回去救他吗
Should we go back and rescue him?
太迟了
It's too late.
他成人礼[13年后]的时候我们再见吧
We'll see him at his Bar Mitzvah.
给你
Here you go.
我买了中式餐回来  跟莱纳德以前买的一样
I picked up the Chinese food just the way Leonard used to.
-这是宫保鸡丁吗  -是的
- Is it kung pao chicken? - Yes.
-糙米  不是精米吧  -不是
- Brown rice, not white rice? - Yes.
-韩国熟食店买的辣酱吗  -是的
- Spicy mustard from the Korean deli? - Yes.
-我很厉害吧  -没错
- I did good, right? - Yes.
艾米
Amy,
你有没有担心我们住在一起
are you worried that us living together
会令我们之间的神秘感消失呢
will take the mystery out of our relationship?
没有
No.
也是  你哪可能啊
Yeah, why would you?
还有  看这个
Oh, and, uh, check this out.
我擅自作主
I took the liberty of scripting
为我们写了电话答录机留言
a new outgoing voice mail message for both of us.
"你好  我是谢尔顿"
"Hello. This is Sheldon."
"我是艾米"
"And this is Amy."
"我们现在不在家"
"We're not home right now."
"因为我们忙着教育大家呢  小子[说唱常用语]"
"'Cause we out dropping science, son."
"请留言"
"Leave a message."
哔
Beep.
你不能住在这里
You can't live here.
什么  为什么呀
What? Why?
你不喜欢这个留言吗
Is it the message?
我使用都市俚语是为了显得咱们不好惹
I only used urban slang to sound tough
-这样人家不会来偷东西  -不是
- so people wouldn't break in. - No.
不关留言的事
It's not the message.
那是因为什么
Well, what is it, then?
我都是按照你喜欢的方式来做事的
I did everything just the way you like it.
-是的  -那他妈的是怎么原因  谢尔顿
- You did. - Then what the hell, Sheldon?!
我们恋爱超过两年了
We have been going out for over two years,
我对你还不够有耐心吗
and I have been nothing but patient with you!
我看你喜欢的傻缺太空电影
I watch your dopey space movies.
我签署你那荒谬的恋爱合约
I signed your ridiculous contract.
我甚至不再擦润唇膏  因为你说
I even stopped wearing lip gloss 'cause you said
那样我的嘴唇看起来太滑了
it made my mouth look too slippery.
你再也找不到
I am the best girlfriend
比我更好的女朋友了
you're ever gonna have.
给我一个为什么我不能住这里的好理由
You give me one good reason why I can't live here.
全是佩妮的错
It's Penny's fault.
什么
What?
她不想和莱纳德一起住
She doesn't want to live with Leonard,
所以他必须回来和我住
so he has to come live here again.
她是我们伊甸园里的毒蛇
She's the snake in our garden.
她是我们不能做亚当夏娃快乐生活的元凶
She's the reason we can't be happy.
艾艾
Hey, Ames. Yeah.
别跟我套近乎
"Hey, Ames," Nothing.
我都已经准备好搬去谢尔顿家了
I was all set to move in with Sheldon,
现在我知道不行
and now I hear I can't
-因为你不想和莱纳德一起住  -什么
- 'cause you don't want to live with Leonard. - What?
谢尔顿  你说了什么
Sheldon, what did you say?
我说了实话
I said the truth.
你不想和莱纳德一起住  你心知肚明
You don't want to live with Leonard, and you know it.
你什么时候开始不想和我一起住
Since when don't you want to live with me?
别冲我发火
Oh, don't get all huffy.
是你自作主张决定搬进来
You're the one who decided to move in
问都没问过我是否准备好了
without even asking me if I was ready.
我认为应该好好说说这点
Yeah, I think we should talk about that.
既然你这么喜欢说出真相
And since you love the truth so much,
你为什么不告诉艾米你不想和她一起住
why don't you tell Amy you don't want to live with her
别用我做替罪羊
instead of blaming it on me?
我以为我们在说另一件事
I thought we were talking about the other thing.
你是个胆小鬼
You're a coward.
好吧  证据的确支持这一论点
Well, the evidence does support that.
来吧  艾米  我们去喝点红酒
Come on, Amy, let's go drink wine
然后吐槽下我们的男朋友有多混蛋
and talk about what jerks our boyfriends are.
知道怎样才能让他们明白吗
You know what would show them?
我应该搬来和你一起住
I should move in here with you.
你想不想
Do you want to...
追几集新的《行尸走肉》
catch up on some Walking Dead?
好吧
Okay.
你有看过洛丽死的那集吗
Have you seen the one where Lori dies?
没有
No.
也许她没死呢
Or maybe she doesn't.
咱们来看看吧
Let's find out.
-你想去哪里  -不要
- Where you going? - No!